http://www.bluerockgolfcourse.com/bluerock/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyBlue Rock Golf Course Privacy PolicyWe at Blue Rock Golf Course are consumers too, and we know how much we value our own privacy. As such, we take the protection of your personal information seriously. In safeguarding your privacy, we collect and maintain only the personal information necessary to provide services you request, and we protect this information from unauthorized use. We also provide you with a method to remove your personally-identifiable data from our systems, should you choose to do so.How We Use Information We Collect and ReceiveWhen you request information, purchase products or services from us, or request to join our email list, we may use information that we collect about you to:Process payments and deliver products and services you have requestedManage your account and provide you with customer supportCommunicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about our products or services that may be of interest to youEnforce our terms and conditionsProtect against or identify possible fraudulent transactionsIf you initiate a transaction with us, we collect and store information about you, such as your name, phone number, address, email, and payment information, as well as any other information you provide to us, in order to process your transactions and send communications about them to you. This information may be shared with select third parties solely for purposes of servicing the transaction. When you submit credit card numbers, we encrypt that information using industry standard technology.Blue Rock Golf Course limits access to your personal information to those employees and business partners (e.g., our online tee times booking provider) who need such information to perform essential functions relating to your request or purchase.Blue Rock Golf Course does not sell, rent or give your personal information to any third party not working directly for us unless requested by a court of law having jurisdiction over that specific information.Third Party Service ProvidersWe may rely on third party providers, including online travel agency sites, to support or provide some services available through the website, such as reservations. We may also rely on third party providers to perform certain services for us in connection with your use of the site, such as network security, customer support, tracking and reporting functions, quality assurance testing, payment processing, our own marketing, and other functions. We may share information from or about you with these third party providers so that they can perform their services or complete your requests. Our website may link to third party services such as a business’s URL. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with these services.Links to Third Party Sites & Third Party AdvertisementsBlue Rock Golf Course accepts no liability for the condition or content of third party websites that may be accessed from the Blue Rock Golf Course website. Except as Blue Rock Golf Course may specifically direct otherwise, we do not authorize the content of those third party websites. The third party advertiser is solely responsible to you for any representations or offers made by it, and for any goods or services that you agree to purchase from those third parties.Data RetentionWe will retain your information only as long as necessary to provide you with the Services or as otherwise set forth in this Policy. We will also retain and use this information as necessary for the purposes set out in this Policy and to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements and protect Blue Rock Golf Course’s legal rights.We also collect and maintain aggregated, anonymized or pseudonymized information which we may retain indefinitely to protect the safety and security of our website, improve our Services or comply with legal obligations.Your Right to Access, Correct, or Request Deletion of your DataUsers residing in certain countries, including the EU, are afforded certain rights regarding their personal information. Except where an exception or exemption applies, these rights include the ability to access, correct, and request deletion of your personal information. To modify or delete the personal information you’ve provided to us, please contact us at privacy@redjacketresorts.com or the address provided at the end of this Policy.Choices You May Make Regarding Your Personal InformationPromotional EmailsYou may choose to provide us with your email address to allow us to send newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials to you, as well as targeted offers from third parties. You can stop receiving promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions in emails that you receive.Promotional MailingsIf at any time you do not want to receive printed or emailed offers from us you may remove yourself from our mailing list by contacting us at the address below. Although we will remove your name from our mailing list after receiving your request, you may still receive mailings from us that were initiated prior to your name being removed.Changes to or Deletion of Your Personal InformationTypically, we retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. In addition, we may keep your Personal Information as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements. You may, however, request that we delete your Personal Information by contacting us at the address below and we will delete such Personal Information to the extent required by law.Access to Your Personal InformationIf required by law, upon request, we will grant you reasonable access to the Personal Information that we have about you. You may request access to your Personal Information by contacting us at the address below.CookiesWhen you visit our website, we may place cookies on your device to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit and links you click. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. You may also clear or delete existing cookies from standard internet browsers.We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our website. This information includes your anonymized IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us, and the referring website address.We may use standard internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site. We also may include web beacons in promotional emails to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors and to measure the effectiveness of our online advertising, content, and other activities.You may set some cookie preferences through your device or browser settings but doing so may affect the functionality of the website. The method for disabling cookies may vary by device and browser but can usually be found in your device or browser preferences or security settings.Legal InformationLegal DisclaimerThis website and its contents (“Website”) are owned by Blue Rock Golf Course, 48 Todd Road, South Yarmouth, MA, 02664. By accessing or using this website, you agree to accept and comply with the terms, conditions, notices and disclaimers contained in these terms and conditions, the Privacy Policy and elsewhere on the website (known collectively as “Terms and Conditions”). The Terms and Conditions govern the use of this website. Blue Rock Golf Course reserves the right to amend these Terms and Conditions at any time without notice.Applicable LawThe Terms and Conditions are governed by and to be construed in accordance with the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts and the State of New Hampshire, USA. You irrevocably and unconditionally agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Massachusetts. The Terms and Conditions are governed by and to be construed in accordance with the laws of Massachusetts. You irrevocably and unconditionally agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Massachusetts. In the event that any provision of the Terms and Conditions is held to be invalid, illegal or unenforceable, that provision must to the extent of the invalidity, illegality or unenforceability be ignored and all the other provisions of the Terms and Conditions will remain in full force and effect. Blue Rock Golf Course makes no representation that the content of the website complies with the laws of any country outside the United States. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.Disclaimer and LiabilityThis website is provided on an “as is” basis. While Blue Rock Golf Course has used its best endeavors to ensure that the information contained on and accessed through the website is correct and current at the time of publication, Blue Rock Golf Course does not accept responsibility for any error, omission or defect in the information.To the fullest extent permissible by law, Blue Rock Golf Course, its affiliated companies and their respective directors, employees, agents and contractors: (a) Do not make any representation, warranty or endorsement of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of the website, your access to the website or results of your access, or the information, content, materials or products on the website; and (b) Do not warrant that the functions on the website will be uninterrupted or error-free, that any defects will be corrected or that the server, which stores and transmits content to you is free of viruses or other harmful components.Subject to any non-excludable liability for breach of conditions or warranties implied by legislation and to the maximum extent permitted by law, under no circumstances (including but not limited to any act or omission on the part of Blue Rock Golf Course, its affiliated companies or their respective directors, employees, agents and contractors) will Blue Rock Golf Course, its affiliated companies or their respective directors, employees, agents or contractors accept liability for any indirect, incidental, special and/or consequential damages or loss of profits resulting from any use or access, or any inability to use or access the website.IndemnityYou agree to indemnify and keep indemnified Blue Rock Golf Course, its affiliated companies and their officers, employees, agents and contractors (“those indemnified”) in respect of any claim, liability, loss, damage, cost (including legal cost) or expense which those indemnified may suffer or incur as a direct or indirect result of your willful or negligent act or omission with respect to the your use of the website (or any part of it) or the violation of these Terms and Conditions by you, or the infringement by you, of any intellectual property or other right of any person or entity.Intellectual Property & Restrictions On Use Of ContentThe website is subject to copyright under United States law and, under international treaties, and the laws of many other countries. The website contains trademarks, intellectual property and copyright protected works, which is owned by Blue Rock Golf Course, and third parties. Except for the direct purpose of viewing, accessing or interacting with the website for your own personal use or as otherwise indicated on the website or these Terms and Conditions, you must not copy, communicate to the public, adapt, transfer, distribute or store any of the contents of the website, or incorporate any part of the website into another website without Blue Rock Golf Course’s express consent.User Submitted ContentWhen you submit any materials via the Blue Rock Golf Course website or its branded social media pages including comments, recordings and images (“Content”), you, unless Blue Rock Golf Course advises otherwise, license and grant Blue Rock Golf Course its affiliates and sub-licensees a non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, worldwide, irrevocable, and sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish and display such Content for any purpose in any media, without compensation, restriction on use, attribution or liability. You agree not to assert any moral rights in relation to such use. You warrant that you have the full authority to grant these rights.You agree that you are fully responsible for the Content you submit. Blue Rock Golf Course shall not be liable in any way for such Content to the full extent permitted by law. Blue Rock Golf Course may remove any Content without notice for any reason whatsoever.You Warrant and AgreeYou will not submit any Content that is unlawful or fraudulent, or that Blue Rock Golf Course may deem in breach of any intellectual property, privacy, publicity or other rights, defamatory, obscene, derogatory, pornographic, sexually inappropriate, violent, abusive, harassing, threatening, objectionable with respect to race, religion, origin or gender, not suitable for children aged under 15, or otherwise unsuitable for publication;You will obtain prior consent from any person or property that appears in your Content;You will obtain full prior consent from any person who has jointly created or has any rights in the Content, to the uses and terms herein;Your Content shall not contain viruses or malware or cause injury or harm to any person or entity;You will comply with all applicable laws and regulations, including without limitation, those governing copyright, content, defamation, privacy, publicity and the access or use of others’ computer or communication systems.Without limiting any other terms herein, you will indemnify Blue Rock Golf Course for any breach of the above terms.Termination and CancellationBlue Rock Golf Course reserves the right in its sole discretion to revise the content of, amend links from, or withdraw access to the website, at any time without notice. Without limiting the operation of any other Terms and Conditions herein, Blue Rock Golf Course will not be held liable for loss or damage arising from the exercising of these rights. Any indemnities given by you and limitations on Blue Rock Golf Course liability will survive such termination.Electronic Systems ComplianceOur online reservations provider is PCI-DSS compliant and uses Go Daddy Secure Certificate Authority SSL Web Server Certificates to ensure secure communications by encrypting all data to and from the website with industry-standard 128-bit secure encryption. Similarly, our internal property management computer systems are physically and electronically isolated and use routinely-updated firewall and software protection to prevent outside intrusion.No method of transmission over the internet or electronic storage is completely secure, so Blue Rock Golf Course cannot guarantee its absolute security, but we are committed to doing our best to ensure that any personal information you entrust to us is secure.How to Contact UsBlue Rock Golf Course Attn: Data Protection Officer 48 Todd Rd. South Yarmouth, MA privacy@redjacketresorts.comUpdated December, 2020Blue Rock Golf Course48 Todd Road South Yarmouth, MA 02664TEL: (508) 398-9295Accessibility Statement Privacy Policy Latest From the Blog2020 par 3 championship resultsNovember 5, 2020 - 11:11 amNew Superintendent Named at Blue Rock Golf CourseSeptember 25, 2020 - 2:39 pmGOLF IS BACK AT BLUE ROCK GOLF COURSE!May 8, 2020 - 2:09 pmConnect With UsVisit The Course Scroll to top Accessibility
B&C
Contrasts Dark
Contrasts White
Stop Movement
Readable Font
Underline Links A A Acancel accessibility
Accessibility Statement
Provided by:
